Now you've had a chance to try out SageMaker's hyperparameter tuning for yourself,
你已经尝试过 SageMaker 的超参数优化功能
let's take a look at my solutions.
下面看看我的实现方法
So as I mentioned earlier,
正如我之前提到的
the first three steps are the same as the other mini-project that we worked on,
前三步与我们完成的其他迷你项目一样
so I've already executed those cells.
我已经执行了这些单元格
Starting here with step four,
从第 4 步开始
the first thing of course that we do,
第一步是
is make sure that we split our dataset up into a validation and training set,
将数据集拆分成验证集和训练集
and then save those datasets to our Notebook Instance.
然后将这些数据集保存到 Notebook 实例中
Once we have our datasets saved to our local notebook instance,
将数据集保存到本地 Notebook 实例中后
we use the upload data method,
使用 upload_data 方法
to upload those datasets to S3.
将这些数据集上传到 S3
Next we do the same thing that we did in the other mini-project,
然后像在其他迷你项目中一样
in that we first get a little bit of information about our current Notebook instance,
首先获取关于当前 Notebook 实例的信息
including both our current role,
包括当前的角色
and the name of the container,
以及容器的名称
that is specific to the region that we are currently working in.
该容器特定于我们当前所在的区域
Just like in the previous Notebooks,
像之前的 Notebook 一样
the first thing to do,
首先
is create an estimator object.
创建一个 estimator 对象
Here I've created an estimator object,
我像之前的 XGBoost
in the same way that we did in the previous XGBoost sentiment analysis Notebook.
Sentiment Analysis Notebook 一样创建了一个 estimator 对象
Furthermore, I just use the same hyperparameters that we used last time as well,
此外 我使用了和上次一样的超参数
including making sure to change the objective to binary logistic.
包括将 objective 设为 binary:logistic
Now that we've created an estimator object,
我们已经创建了 estimator 对象
which serves as the basic model
它将作为 SageMaker 超参数优化作业的
which SageMaker will use in the hyperparameter tuning job,
基本模型
we need to set up the hyperparameter tuner object.
下面我们需要设置 HyperparameterTuner 对象
Like we discussed in the last video,
就像在上个视频中讨论的那样
we first provide the estimator object,
首先指定 estimator 对象
which is the base model,
它将是基准模型
we then say which metric we would like to optimize, in our case,
然后指定要优化的指标
again, we'll be using RMSE,
我们将使用
of the validation set.
验证集的 RMSE
Then we describe what makes a model better.
然后指定什么样的模型更好
In this case it is having a smaller RMSE value.
即更小的 RMSE 值
Next we tell SageMaker the total number of models we'd like it to create for us.
接着指定模型总数
In this case, I've just chosen six,
我设成了 6
because each of these training jobs takes a bit longer than the Boston Housing example.
因为每个训练作业都比 Boston Housing 示例的运行时间更长
So I don't want to wait too long.
我不想等太久
Next we tell SageMaker how many models should be created in parallel.
接着指定并行运行的模型数量
Lastly, we describe the ranges that we want various parameters to take on.
最后 指定各个参数的范围
Now that we've created the hyperparameter tuner object,
创建好 HyperparameterTuner 对象后
we just ask SageMaker to train it.
要求 SageMaker 训练它
As we discussed, this is all going on in the background.
正如之前讨论的 所有这些都在后台运行
So, we just wait for it to finish.
所以等待运行完毕